Assembly of Governmental Employees Records 5769
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Assembly of Governmental Employees Records
1973-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Assembly of Governmental Employees
5769
20 cubic feet
20 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3123982
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, January 22, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3035: Eric Polisar Papers 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Assembly of Governmental Employees (Washington, D.C.)
3123982
- General Assembly material 1981, 1982 minutes, 1983 Registration forms; Board minutes 1983-1984, 1980-1982, 1963-1975; Member mailings 1981-1982, 1982-1983, 1983-1984 (inc. registration for 1984 assembly); Assoc. files.. (Box 1)
  - 30th Annual Age General Meeting, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1983 General Assembly (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 29th General Assembly Aug 20-21, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1982 General Assembly (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly Minutes 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Assistance Program, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Credentials Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Audit Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1984 Committee: General Information (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Policy Review Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Resolutions Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Retirement Study Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rules Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sergeants-at-Arms, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Women in the Public Sector, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 10 Outstanding Legislators Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ten Outstanding Leg., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General Assembly -and- Critique Committee, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Registrations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Registrations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 84 Registration Receipt Forms, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Louisville Gen. Assn. Registrations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Certification of Delegates, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1984 General Assembly (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Louisville 1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Assembly of Governmental Employees, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Comp-U-Card, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Age Board Mtg. Aug. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Age Board Mtg. Aug. 18, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board Meeting April 6-7, 1987, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - AGE Board Mtg. Dec. 13, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- General Assembly material 1981, 1982 minutes, 1983 Registration forms; Board minutes 1983-1984, 1980-1982, 1963-1975; Member mailings 1981-1982, 1982-1983, 1983-1984 (inc. registration for 1984 assembly); Assoc. files.. (Box 2)
  - Board Meetings - Minutes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board Meetings - Minutes, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board Meeting - Minutes, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board Meeting - Minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Staff Benefit Bank Transactions (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Age Board Minutes 3-19-83 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board Mtg Aug 18, 1982 Asheville NC (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board Conference Call + Meeting, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AGE Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board Minutes for Aug. 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AGE Board Mtg. Aug. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board Meeting April 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dec. 1-2, 1981 Board Meeting Washington D.C. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - AGE Bd. Meeting Feb. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Member Mail for Sept. 1985 to Sept. 1984, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mail to Affiliates 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mail to Affiliates 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- General Assembly material 1981, 1982 minutes, 1983 Registration forms; Board minutes 1983-1984, 1980-1982, 1963-1975; Member mailings 1981-1982, 1982-1983, 1983-1984 (inc. registration for 1984 assembly); Assoc. files.. (Box 3)
  - Alabama State Employees Association, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Arkansas Public Employees Association, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Indiana State Employees Association, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Kansas Assn. of Public Employees, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Kentucky - Misc., 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Maryland Classified Employees Assn., 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma Public Employees Association, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Independent State Store Union, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - South Carolina State Employees Association, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - South Dakota State Employees Organization, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Texas Public Employees Assoc., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vermont State Employees Association, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Governmental Employees Association, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Washington Public Employees Association, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Alaska Public Employees Association, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Arizona Pea, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Arkansas Pea, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - California State EA, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - (CA) Smud, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Colorado Ape, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Idaho Pea, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Illinois Sea, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Maryland SEA, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kansas SEA, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Baltimore CMEA, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Michigan SEA, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Minnesota (Image), 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Missouri Ape, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Montana Public Employees Association, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Nebraska Association of Public Employees, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Carson City EA (NV), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - (Nev) Carson - Tahoe Hospital Emp. Assn., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - SEA New Hampshire, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - New Mexico State Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - State Employees od North Carolina was NCSEA and NCSGEA Up to 1984 July (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - North Dakota State Employees Assn., 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Tennessee SEA, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Utah PEA, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Vermont SEA, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Washington SEA, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - West Virginia PEA, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Wisconsin, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Wyoming Public Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - CIPEC - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - CIPEC, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - California - Potentials, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - (Calif) Contra Costa County Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - (Calif) Pub. Emp. Assn. of Riverside County, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - (Calif)) San Joaquin County Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - (Calif) butte County Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Monterey County EA, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - (CA) Orange County Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - San Bernandino Public Emp. Assn., 1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - California School Employees Association, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - (Conn) Civil Service Emp. Affiliates, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Connecticut State Employees Association., 1980 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- As above (member mailings, files); General Files A-E. (Box 4)
  - Florida (Miscellaneous), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Florida State Employees Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Georgia State Employees Association (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts State Employees Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Maine State Employees Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Maine SEA, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Minnesota Association of Pub. Emp., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - (Miss.) Public Employees Association, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - (Miss) State Emp. Assn. of Mississippi, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Troopers Coalition, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - State of Nevada Employees Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Civil Serv. Assn., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Civil Service Employees of New York, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ohio Assn. of Public School Employees, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ohio Civil Service Employees Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ohio Public Workers Union, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Oregon State Employees Association, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Puerto Rico, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tennessee State Employees Association, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Texas Public Employees Association, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - (Wash.) Classified Staff Association, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ten Outstanding State Legis. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Executive Director Advisory Council/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Needs Assessment 10/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Age Directory 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Address Changes, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - AACSE (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Atlantic Division, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Pacific Division, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Vermont, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Asheville Gen. Assn. 1982 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Nashville General Assembly - 1981 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Dec. 1. 1981 - VP Bush's Task Force on Regulatory Relief (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Photographs
  - Stephens, Robert (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Photograph
  - McIntosh, Robert J. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - CONSSS, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - C.C.P.R. Coordinating Council on Public Retirement, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Council of Age Attorneys, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Council of Age Ex. Dir., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Robert Pruim Memoranda, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Crage Board Notes, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Deferred Compensation H.R. 3215, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Erage, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Erage: Board Notes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- General Files F-Legislation. (Box 5)
  - Age Fund, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Film Catalog, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Insurance Programs (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - General Questionnaires, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Group Legal Services, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Intergovernmental Personnel Act, 1970-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - I.P.M.A., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Reports, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Social Security Bills, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - S.S. Offset, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - A-122, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - House Bills, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Senate Bills, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - S. 655/ H.R. 1983 Mathias Canable Unitary Apportionment, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - H.R.3616 - State Police Subsistence + Int. Rev. Code, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Postal - Non-Profit, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 4738 Wagner- Peyser Act., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Employment Security Funding, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - P.E.R.I.S.A. Peppra, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Wage and Price Standards, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - General Masters (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - ADEA Exemption for Public Safety Employees, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Deferred Comp Plans - to raise Maximum Dollar Limit Deferred (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Employee Benefit Taxation, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - PEPPRA 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Employment Security Issues, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Post Office, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Merit System, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Policy File (Masters), 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 10 Outstanding 1983 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Certificates, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Outstanding State Legislators, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- General Files-Legislation-Retirement Housing. (Box 6)
  - Membership, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NCPERS, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Nationwide Insurance Policies, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Nationwide Insurance, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - National Pharmacies, 1980-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - International Travel Card, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Labor-Management Relations Svc., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Advertising Cost, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Endorsements, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Merit Legislation, 1974-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Original Forms (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Pebsco, 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - President's Commission on Pension Policy, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Post Office, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - City Duplicating, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Government Printing Office, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - City Duplicating Center, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Public Employees round-Table, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Recruitment - Employment Opportunities, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Retirement Housing, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- General Files-Retirement Income. (Box 7)
  - AGE, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Assembly of Government Employees, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Assembly of Government Employees, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - IRS Reports/ Returns, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Administration Correspondence, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Forms and TIRs. And Compliance Material, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Labor Report/Returns, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - AGE Retirement Plan, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - San Joaquin - Pension Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - AGE, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Exemplar Drafts of Plan from Nationwide (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Board, Resolution Memo, Nationwide Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- General Files-SAGE-W.A.G.E.. (Box 8)
  - Sage, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Staff Benefits, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Statement of Financial Condition (Yearly), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - T.D.X., 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tax Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Directory Changes of Age Affiliates and Independent Public Employee Organizations, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Trans National A Special Membership Services Company, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Trans National, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Travel Report, 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - W.A.G.E., 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - W.A.G.E., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Wage Board Notes, 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Wage Salt Cake, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Affirmative Action-Civil Service-Merit Systems. (Box 9)
  - Affirmative Action, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Agency Shop, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholism, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - American Arbitration Association (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Political Coercion, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - West Virginia PEA Anti-Political Coercion Case, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Association Discount Programs, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bakke Decision, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining Elections, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - The Mercer Public Sector Report, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Benefits, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Bibliography Sources, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Career Training, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Chapter Publications, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Child Care, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Civil Service- Merit Systems, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Civil Service-Merit Systems-Comparable Worth. (Box 10)
  - Civil Service-Merit Systems, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Merit Principle Protection, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Collective Bargaining Contracts: School Employees, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining: Private Industry, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining Training, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining Misc., 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Scope of Bargaining, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Employment Training Act, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Comparable Worth, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Constitution & Bylaws-Employee Evaluations. (Box 11)
  - Age Regions - CBL's, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Convention Representation and Election of Officers, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1975-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ex-Director Role (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Automatic Dues Increases (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Constitutions + Bylaws, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Consumer Price Index, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correctional Officers, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Davis-Bacon, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Deferred Compensation, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Discrimination, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Dues Deductions and Authorization Cards, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Employee Assistance Programs, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - EEOC (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Employee Attitude Surveys, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Employee Evaluations, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- "Employee of the Year"-Health Care. (Box 12)
  - "Employee of the Year" (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Employee Rights, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - E.R.A., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ethics Legislation, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Federal Labor Relations Decisions, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Federal Pay, 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Job Sharing, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Flexitime, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Grievance Procedures State by State, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Grievance Proc. Handling Association's Policies, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hatch Act, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Hazardous Duty Pay, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - I.C.E.T. Program Hwy. Dept., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Impasse, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Health Care, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Insurance Programs-Labor Unions-SEIU. (Box 13)
  - Insurance Programs, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Job Descriptions, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Job Representatives, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Job Seniority, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Labor Legislation, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - AFGE, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO Public Employee Department, 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Labor Unions - AFSCME, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - AFT, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - C.H. American Nurses Association, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CWA, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Labor Unions - ICPA, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - N.A.G.E., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - IBPO, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - NEA, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Laborers' International Union, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Retail Clerks International, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees (RWDSU), 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - SIEU, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Labor Unions-Teamsters-New Member Letters. (Box 14)
  - Teamsters, 1979-1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Labor Union Salaries, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Labor Unions Miscellaneous, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Union, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Layoff Procedures, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Leave on Absence Union Business (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Legal Cases, 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Legal Services, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hatch Act, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Legislation - Healthcare, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Legislation - Humphrey Hawkins, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Legislation - Labor Reform, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Minimum Wage, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Legislation - No Fault, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Taxation of Education Benefits, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Taxation of Fringe Benefits, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Welfare Reform HR 1538, H.R. 4321, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Legislation - Whistleblowers, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Meat and Poultry Inspection Programs, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Membership Surveys, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Negotiation Handbooks (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - New Member Letters, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Occupational Safety & Health Standards-Proposition 13. (Box 15)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Standards (OSHA), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Perdiem/Mileage, 1979-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Investment of Pension Funds, 1978-1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Pension Bill, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Weather Closings, 1979-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Jury Duty, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Personnel Rules and Regulations, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Rules and Regulations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Political Action/ Political Activity, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Productivity, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Proposition 13, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Productivity-Sick Leave. (Box 16)
  - Productivity, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Public Employee Labor Relations Boards, 1975-1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1968-1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Retirement, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Retirement, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Right to Work, 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Salary Surveys, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sick Leave Incentive Programs, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Sick Leave, 1978-1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Social Security-Workmen's Compensation. (Box 17)
  - Social Security, 1977-1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Social Security, 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Staff Information, 1975-1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Staff Training (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Sunset Laws, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Supervisors, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Supreme Court Cases, 1976-1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Taxation of Fringe Benefits, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Unemployment, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Van Pools, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Women, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Publications. (Box 18)
  - AGE, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The Push to Affiliate/A Study of State Government Employment Benefits, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - AGE, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - A Study of State Government Employee Benefits, 1978-1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - AGE Public Employee, 1977-1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - AGE, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Updates, 1979-1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - AGE, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Dollars and Sense: The Case for State and Local Pension Reform, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Conference on Public Employee Retirement Systems, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Summary of Public Sector Labor Relations Policies, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Labor-Management Relations in State and Local Governments, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Labor-Management Relations in States and Local Governments, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - How to Prepare a Sound Pay Plan, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Public Employment in 1983 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Public Employment in 1983 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - The Use of Economic Data in Collective Bargaining, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - The Use of Economic Data in Collective Bargaining, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - NTPA '84, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - The Book of The States, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Passing the Bucks, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Pension Task Force Report on Public Employee Retirement Systems, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Publications. (Box 19)
  - Out of Binder 1, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Out of Binder 1, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)